

Falmouth, Cornwall, United Kingdom

Summary_

I am an avid programmer and passionate producer, with a strong knowledge of version control using Git, agile methodology, and an excitement for facing new, interesting challenges. I have lead teams which have published to both Itch and Steam, always with a focus on maintaining healthy and flexible working practices. My ideal position would be a Graduate/ Junior Producer role, with a strong focus on growing my skills and experience so I could progress to a more senior position.

Skills

- · Project Management: Jira, Confluence, Trello, Agile
- Version Control: Git
- · Game Engines: Unity, Unreal Engine 4
- Languages: C#, C++, Latex

Published Games_

Project: Silverback - Producer & Team Lead

Unity 2020.3

IN DEVELOPMENT

September 2021 - Current

- Made the decision alongside my team to cancel a project in pre-production to develop this game instead
- · Developed a Github Action workflow to automatically build, test & publish daily builds to Steam
- Utilised Story Points, Release Planning, and Jira to produce a development roadmap

Carma - Producer & Team Lead

Unity 2019.4

SELF PUBLISHED TO STEAM (HTTPS://STORE.STEAMPOWERED.COM/APP/1603990/CARMA/)

Published June 2021

- Worked with a multidisciplinary team to bring Carma from concept to published game
- Planned sprints and development milestones using Agile
- Removed blockers and streamlined development pipelines
- · Focused on maintaining team health and reinforcing healthy working practices
- Set up Steam store and maintained updated builds

Yvaga Station - Team Lead & Programmer

Unity 2018.4

SELF PUBLISHED TO ITCH.IO (HTTPS://DAYLUKE.ITCH.IO/YVAGA-STATION)

Published May 2020

- Presented a concept pitch to in order to continue development past prototype stage
- Implemented asymmetric multiplayer game using PUN2 package for networking
- · Designed and implemented a modular custom movement system to expand on the options available to the player

Education

Falmouth University BSc Computing For Games

Falmouth, United Kingdom

Sept. 2019 - June 2022

· Worked with multi-discipline teams to bring several games through a full development cycle

Work Experience _____

Director Falmouth, Cornwall

GLASS NOMAD GAMES • Started a company to publish video games my team and I were developing

• Handled registration and set up with services such as Steam

Senior Ambassador Falmouth, Cornwall

FXPLUS

- Promoted from Student Ambassador
- Increased responsibility for the smooth running of events
- Manages the distribution of Student Ambassadors during events
- Relied on to handle any complications or problems that arise during an event

June 2020 - Current

March 2021 - Current